My brother's...
rather, Gilbert's mansion
has been searched.
Documents connected to the
plot to murder Your Majesty
were found hidden in rooms underground.
I see. So they've found
concrete evidence.
Albert Ararat
Crown Prince, Second Prince
That fool isn't even worthy
of comparison to a dog.
And what will be done with him?
Premeditated murder of the
emperor is undeniably treason.
Under imperial law, there is no choice
but to cut him in half at the waist.
I see.
However, this case could be perceived
as merely attempted murder.
And what would that entail?
He isn't exempt from being cut in half,
but he can still be granted the
minimum stay of execution.
His sentence would then be carried out
only when Your Majesty orders it.
Why complicate the matter like that?
It's still execution by cutting in half.
If he's to be executed anyway, what
does it matter when it's done?
No, Noah has yet again proven wise.
He has considered this from both
legal and emotional perspectives.
I appreciate you giving it such thought.
Gilbert is still the emperor's son.
Keeping in mind that he might love
him too much to execute him,
I gave him an option that would
essentially result in a life sentence.
There is no need for hesitation.
Those who attempted to kill you with
poison deserve immediate death.
Albert.
I leave his execution in your hands. Go.
Yes, sire.
He really thought he could
get his hands on the crown.
Pitiful.
Noah.
You were right to tell me that.
How brilliant of you to show such
consideration in these circumstances.
I feel your consideration has
brought some degree of salvation.
Personally, I would like to transfer
ownership of Gilbert's fief to you.
You mustn't.
What?
I informed you of Gilbert's
plot confidentially.
If I were to receive his fief now,
the other princes would start making
all kinds of reports anonymously
and sabotage each other in hopes
of earning the same reward.
Now, slow down.
I only said I would like to do that.
I don't mind my sons competing,
but I can't have them trying
to sabotage each other.
So I will not reward you this time.
I understand.
Instead, I will merely do
that which is expected.
You will soon be relocating
to your own fief.
It's time to start thinking
about your future wife.
Yes, sire.
Engagement by age twelve is not
unusual in the imperial family.
And a prince's first wife—his legal
wife, as opposed to a concubine—
is chosen for 100% political reasons,
and must have standing
befitting the role.
For that reason, the prince himself has
essentially no say in who he marries.
However, it is possible
for fate to play a part.
How about the granddaughter of
my uncle, the Lightning Prince?
The Lightning Prince...
I believe he's been retired and out
of politics for many years already.
Divination has revealed that you and
she will have a very clever child.
I would only place the
probability around 1%,
but that child may even be
more brilliant than you.
Nothing would make me happier than to
take someone so remarkable as my wife.
In that case, I will initiate
the marriage negotiations.
Yes, sire.
My, Prince Noah never ceases to amaze.
He didn't even know the girl's
name or anything else about her.
That's what it means to be a
prince—part of an imperial family.
True, but it's natural for a young man
to take an interest in his future wife.
To get past that at such a young age...
What can it be called but amazing?
"Choose a grandchild as your successor."
"A good grandchild guarantees
three generations of prosperity."
It is indeed a good idea.
But how likely is it, truly, that
my grandchild could surpass me?
At the moment, all that potential
lies with Prince Noah.
If his brilliance passes
down to his child...
I see.
All we can do is hope, then.
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
I am resigned to my fate.
I make no excuses for my betrayal of
Prince Gilbert, my former master.
Please, at least, make it quick.
Don't be so hasty. Who said any of that?
B-But...
People are treasures.
I don't kill them on a whim.
And imperial law says an indicted man
who exposes treason is to be acquitted.
Huh?
I called you here for a few reasons.
First, Gilbert has been executed,
and all power he possessed has collapsed.
So there's no longer any need for you to
change your name and leave the capital.
O-Oh...
And exposing treason is worth
a reward of up to 1,000 rean.
I'll add another zero to
that out of my own pocket.
What? Wh-Why would you
give me so much money?
Because you saved my father's life.
I could return you to the Department
of the Imperial Household
as a member of my household,
but I want to hear what you want.
Incredible...
You are my master for life.
No matter where I go, I will
obey your every command.
I see.
Zoey, you heard that, yes?
Y-Yes.
Your mother is no longer in danger.
Tell her she can rest at ease.
Master, you even
remembered my mother...
Thank you so much.
This is the capital of
a nation of warriors,
Master?
but I have yet to see anyone
who looks like a warrior!
It sounds like something interesting
is going on over there.
Well? Is there anyone who
wishes to challenge me?
All you need to do is fight me and win.
The entry fee is three rean.
And what do we get if we win?
Me.
I'll be your wife, your mistress, your
servant, whatever you tell me to be.
In imperial law, illegal
slave-trading is defined as
"the buying and selling of other people."
Selling oneself doesn't
violate that, but...
So I just gotta defeat you, right?
Yeah, but it has to be one-on-one.
That was my intention from the start.
Otherwise, even if I won,
I'd have to share you!
Three rean.
Huh?
You didn't pay the entry fee.
Oof, that's embarrassing!
He challenged her without paying
and lost within seconds!
Damn it!
Okay, who's next?
That'll be me!
Then I'm after him!
And I'm after him!
Wow! That's fifteen challengers down!
Okay, who's next?
Y-You do it.
No way, man.
I'll do it.
Hey, you need to pay.
There'll be no need for that.
'Cause I'm gonna be the one... to win!
Wh-What just happened?
He beat her that easily...
Now you belong to me.
Hold it.
That has to be against the rules.
Huh?
What's your deal, kid?
Quit griping about—
You used some sort of
numbing drug, didn't you?
If you made someone else
do that, it's two-on-one.
Wh-What are you talking about?!
Where's your proof that—
Found him.
I-I don't know that guy!
Don't lie, Chad!
That's your henchman, Rob!
You were just drinking with
him at my bar yesterday!
Put the girl down, you coward!
Little brat! You'll pay for butting in!
Just look at him now!
That kid's incredible!
He was so fast, I didn't see a thing!
Do you want to continue?
Y-Y-Y...
You're gonna pay for this!
W-Wait for me, Chad!
Are you awake now?
Who are... you?
You ought to be grateful to this boy.
He saved your life, you know.
He did?
How much do you remember?
I remember... fighting with some creep...
and suddenly, my legs
wouldn't move anymore.
He had his friend attack you.
That coward!
I don't deny that, but you
were also too careless.
Why were you out there
doing that, anyway?
Tell me.
I ran out of money...
I came here for the
knight selection exam,
but I didn't make the cut.
I don't even have the money
to go home... so I...
Wait. That doesn't make sense.
What doesn't make sense?!
I saw your skills back there.
You couldn't have failed.
I didn't agree with it either,
so I looked into it.
But then this year's head judge,
the Tenth Prince, summoned me
and said he'd be willing
to let me progress...
but in return, as a woman, I'd have to...
Okay, that's enough. I understand.
That particular brother
is the type to say that.
Do you still want to be a knight?
Of course!
Even if it takes years, I'll
become a knight on my own merit!
Then you don't need to return home.
Here's 100 rean.
It should be enough to live on until
the next knight selection exam.
Wha...
Gigi, see to her living arrangements.
Understood.
Wh-What is this about? Why do all this?
Because I like you.
You want recognition not for your
womanhood, but based on merit.
I like that sort of person.
Who are you? You're not just some kid.
There he is!
That's the brat!
You had some nerve
humiliating me back there!
Boss, you tell 'em, too!
You're—
Stay back.
Oh?
You want to do the honors?
Then I'll link you with
my armor ring and...
There.
Wh-What the hell?!
His fists are on fire!
I've never seen anything
like that before!
Hey! No chickening out! Get him!
R-Rob!
Wow... No wasted movements at all...
He's that strong?
You're not going to fight?
That's the Tenth Prince's knight!
Ah. I get it now.
P-P-P-Please forgive me,
Thirteenth Prince!
I get that they were paid
under the table to do this,
but once they knew who I was,
they thought they could avoid
getting caught if they kept quiet.
Thirteenth... Prince?
You're the Wise Prince,
the minister-prince of justice?!
Yes. Noah Ararat.
The real deal?
Well, that would explain
everything that's happened.
He's a prince and a minister,
but he doesn't flaunt his status at all.
I'll let you handle their punishment.
Did you try to attack me?
I'll let you off the hook
just this once. Take them.
Y-Yes, Your Highness!
Come on, get moving!
What an impressive boy you are.
Your looks and skills are both top-notch.
Who is he?
I don't often see such
remarkable young men.
The Golden Gourd?
I just recently learned
about that and its owner!
It is an honor to meet you,
Your Imperial Highness
the Lightning Prince.
Ah, so you know who I am.
Is that guy a prince, too?
I feel like I've heard
that name before...
The Lightning Prince, Indra Ararat.
A few decades ago, when the current
emperor assumed the throne,
he stood in the center of
power as the Prince Regent.
The empire was in chaos because
the emperor was so young,
but he proved capable enough
to take control of it all.
Five years later, the Prince
Regent stepped aside,
choosing to retire to his
fief without argument...
Lightning
and he earned the title of
"Lightning" for his role
in ushering in the emperor's
new administration.
And now such a great man suddenly
shows up in the capital?
Come over here and sit down.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Episode 10
Lightning Prince and Wise Prince
Since you know who I am...
I assume the emperor has
already spoken to you.
Yes, he spoke to me himself.
I see, I see. Then you also
know why I've come here.
To evaluate me?
The emperor chose you
because he trusts you,
so there's really no need for
me to verify anything...
but this does affect the life
of my granddaughter, after all.
The way he speaks would
make an inspector furious.
Emperor
Uncle
(Lightning Prince)
Indra
Brother
Graeme
Although he is the emperor's
uncle, he remains his subject.
Fourth Prince
Henry
Third Prince
Kiro
(Subjects)
First Prince
Gilbert
Crown Prince,
Second Prince
Albert
For him to simply address him as "the
emperor" is extremely disrespectful.
But... well, I don't think he'd even
care if I called him out on it.
I don't think my father would
find fault with him, either.
That's just how this man is.
What will you do if I don't
measure up to your standards?
I just won't let you
marry her, that's all.
But this was an imperial
command, was it not?
That doesn't mean a thing.
Sure, if it were any other order from
the emperor, I'd obey at any cost.
But this is my granddaughter, you know.
This is my precious little
granddaughter we're talking about.
That means it's not political.
It's personal.
And the one who gave the order is my
nephew, the boy I once bounced on my knee.
If he's wrong, I'll smack him upside the
head if that's what it takes to stop him.
I see. He's an interesting man.
I don't think he has any
desire to gain power.
That's why he doesn't get
rebuked for being rude.
In fact, this is preferred.
So... do I pass?
That's what I'm about to find out.
What is this? It feels like
something's crushing me...
It's just like what I make Leviathan do!
The menace!
In that case...
I'll push back!
Oh?
Good! Now, with one blow...
No, I shouldn't.
He's my great-uncle and, potentially,
my future grandfather-in-law.
I shouldn't injure him in public.
I'll control this so I
neither win nor lose.
Impressive, boy! I admit defeat!
Um... I thought it was a draw...
No, blockhead.
You read my technique perfectly
and made it a draw.
Your mindfulness did me in.
He calls it mindfulness,
but he gave it away himself.
He really is the type of person
you just can't dislike.
I like you, boy.
Take care of my granddaughter.
I will.
I'm in a good mood today!
You there!
Bring out all the booze you've got!
This round's on me!
Everyone who can drink, drink up!
Could he be any more extravagant?
He sure isn't like any
of the nobles I know.
This is yours.
An engagement gift.
A ring?
That there is...
Show me your strength.
What is this place?
"Show me your strength," you say?
Send it flying!
Earth
Light
Dark
It went up.
Light has a +C.
My name is Behemoth.
I surrender to you.
It's called Behemoth.
Its power pairs with mine.
Like this?
Even I couldn't win Behemoth over,
and you did it in a heartbeat!
Even a man as powerful as Your
Highness couldn't win it over?
It only told me its name.
I was hoping I'd get to see that
fantastical golden figure again.
Its figure? Like this?
Yeah! That's it!
You can do that, too?
You're really something, boy!
I can learn powers and abilities
by making it battle.
Make it battle what?
Well...
I think it'd be faster to just show you.
The magic sword of water, Leviathan.
The ring of flame, Luthier.
The painting of wind, Huwawa.
The ring of earth, Behemoth.
It has been a thousand years
since they were all assembled...
not since the Silver Age.
And the Thirteenth Prince...
Yes, he was about to have
a wondrous experience
that could only be called a miracle.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu